It’s for students that are in the art clubs or in Art 11/12, or in Art 8/9.
미술 클럽에 속해있거나 Art 11/12, Art 8/9을 듣는 학생은 미술전시회를 갖습니다
So, in their art classes they make a lot of projects and then they get to put their work up.
미술 수업중 학생은 다양한 프로젝트를 완성해서 자신의 작품을 보여줍니다
They get to put their work up and display their best work.
학생은 본인 작품을 보여줄 최고의 작품을 전시하게 됩니다
They get to choose what their best work is
모든 학생들은 자신만의 제일 멋진 작품을 선정해서
and then every student gets a chance to put their work in the show and show it off
전시회때 뽐낼 수 있는 기회를 갖습니다
Students take a foundations course
학생은 파운데이션 코스를 선택하게 되는데
and that means that they get to do sculpture, they do ceramic,
이는 조각, 세라믹
they do painting, they do collage, they do drawing techniques.
페인팅, 콜라주, 드로잉 기술을 포함합니다
So basically, there’s everything through all those disciplines
기본적으로 모든 훈련을 거치게 되며
and they get to show what their best work was in those projects.
학생은 프로젝트 중 최고의 작품을 보여주게 됩니다
There’s things like masks for “Day of the Dead”
그 중 하나는 ‘Day of the Dead’ 라는 마스크 프로젝트인데
and all my students took part in those masks.
모든 학생들이 참여했습니다
Some students did mosaics,
어떤 학생은 모자이크를
we did a bunch of still life
또 다른 학생은 정물화
and then some students went on field trips
일부 학생들은 필드 트립 등을 선택했습니다
so what’s behind me right here is from a field trip to the Vancouver Art Gallery
현재 제 뒤로는 밴쿠버 아트갤러리 필드 트립 현장인데
and they went to an Emily Carr exhibit and then did a workshop
학생들은 Emily Carr 전시에 와서 워크숍을 가졌습니다
Mashu Higa, actually he is in the North Shore News this week for his art
Mashu Higa는 이번주 North Shore 뉴스에 나오게 되었는데
And he is creating a work on “crowd-sourcing”.
‘크라우드 소싱’ 작품을 만들어서
Getting people together to participate in his art.
사람들이 그의 작품에 참여토록 하고 있습니다
They are putting a pin where they live in the world, where they come from
관람객은 본인이 사는 곳, 출생지 등을 핀으로 표시하고
and then on the piece that he created he drew a piece of himself,
자화상처럼
kind of like a self-portrait
본인을 그린 Mashu 작품 위에
there putting pins where they live or come from and then they are writing a comment
그들의 출신지와 캐나다에 대한
about where they come or about Canada on the piece,
내용들을 적고 있습니다
so they get to actually participate in the piece which is really neat
관람객이 실제로 작품에 참여하는 것이 이색적입니다
Mashu’s work is actually part of his application for Emily Carr,
사실 Mashu의 작품은 Emily Carr대학의 입학을 위한 것이기도 합니다
They get you to do a project, so this is for him to get to work on his application
그 곳에서는 입학 요건으로 프로젝트를 요구하는데
While he is actually in art class
Mashu는 미술 수업 시간에 이 작품을 만들었습니다